Um, I have been of a mind that these folks, the powers that be, they are seeding the waters,
you know, the soil for a civil war that they have been really doing their best to try to
incite a civil war. And I would like to adjust my tune on that. People are waiting for a civil
war to begin thinking that it will be with physical violence. And I would argue that we are
currently in a civil war and it's through emotional and mental violence through parapsychological
violence. The fact that we are gaslit in such a deeply, uh, consistent fashion on, on so many
levels is a form of violence. And anyone who's been a victim of emotional abuse understands that.
And so that's why for a lot of people who don't understand my reasoning for being so repetitive,
redundant, for being what someone called insufferable in my consistent, um, addressing
of the ways in which we are being manipulated, understand that it's because we are currently
at a war for our minds. And I feel like every day I'm waking up to arm myself and do my best
to arm y'all because the physical violence part of the civil war will be at Zenith. We're already
in it. Support a real one.